suredone.com 2019-01-03

# Privacy Policy | SureDone

This Privacy Policy describes how and when SureDone collects, uses and shares your information when you use our Services. SureDone receives your information through our various websites, email notifications, APIs, applications, and commerce services (the " **Services** " or " **SureDone** ") and from our partners and other third parties. For example, you send us information when you use SureDone from our website or a third-party integration partner. When using any of our Services you consent to the collection, transfer, manipulation, storage, disclosure and other uses of your information as described in this Privacy Policy. Irrespective of which country you reside in or supply information from, you authorize SureDone to use your information in the United States and any other country where SureDone operates.

If you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at support@SureDone.com.

The data controller of your personal information is SureDone, Inc. .   
You may contact the data controller by email to support@SureDone.com with the subject line "Re: Data Controller Request" 

### Information Collection and Use

**Account Registration:** When you create or reconfigure a SureDone account, you provide some personal information, such as your name, password, physical address, phone number, business name, and email address. Your business name is listed publicly on our Services, including on your profile page and in search results provided through certain third-party websites. Some Services do not require registration.

**Additional Information:** As part of the registration and account creation process, you may be asked to provide other personally identifying information. Providing some of the requested information is optional and SureDone will indicate what information is required and what information is optional.  You can always choose not to provide information even though it may be needed to make a purchase from a SureDone client or take advantage of our Services or features. 

You may provide us with profile information to make public, such as information about your business, your location, your website, or pictures. We may use your contact information to send you information about our Services or to market to you. You may unsubscribe by following the instructions contained within the notification. If you email us, we may keep your message, email address and contact information to respond to your request. If you connect your SureDone account to your account on another service in order to cross-post between SureDone and that service, the other service may send us your registration or profile information on that service and other information that you authorize. 

**Public Information:** The Services are designed to help SureDone’s clients share information with the world. Most of the information you provide us as a SureDone client is information you are asking us to make public. This includes not only the the products that you post for sale, and media you store on the Services, as well as many other bits of information that result from your use of the Services. Our Services broadly and instantly disseminate your public information to a wide range of users, customers, and services. For instance, your public user profile information and public product listings are immediately delivered via our APIs to our partners and other third parties, including search engines, developers, and publishers that integrate SureDone content into their services.

**Location Information:** You may choose to publish your location in your SureDone profile. You may also tell us your location when you send shipping information or billing information to  SureDone, or your computer or mobile device sends us location information. We may also use other data from your device to determine location, for example, information about wireless networks or cell towers near your mobile device, or your IP address. We may use and store information about your location to provide features of our Services, such as determining product availability with your location, and to improve and customize the Services. 

**Links:** SureDone may keep track of how you interact with links across our Services, including our email notifications, third-party services, and client applications, by redirecting clicks or through other means. We do this to help improve our Services, to provide more relevant advertising, and to be able to share aggregate click statistics such as how many times a particular link was clicked on.

**Cookies:** Like many websites, we use cookies and similar technologies to collect additional website usage data and to improve our Services. A cookie is a small data file that is transferred to your computer's hard disk. SureDone may use both session cookies and persistent cookies to better understand how you interact with our Services, to monitor aggregate usage by our users and web traffic routing on our Services, and to customize and improve our Services. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. You can instruct your browser, by changing its settings, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. 

**Log Data:** When you use our Services, we may receive information (" **Log Data** ") such as your IP address, browser type, operating system, the referring web page, pages visited, location, your mobile carrier, device information (including device and application IDs), search terms, and cookie information. We receive Log Data when you interact with our Services, for example, when you visit our websites, sign into our Services, or interact with our email notifications. We may also receive Log Data when you click on, view or interact with a link to our Services through a third-party application, such as when you choose to purchase an item from a SureDone client through a third-party integration partner, such as eBay or Amazon. SureDone uses Log Data to provide, understand, and improve our Services. 

**Commerce Services:** You may provide your payment information, including your credit or debit card number, card expiration date, CVV code, and billing address (collectively, " **Payment Information** "), along with your shipping address, to complete a commerce transaction on  SureDone or with a SureDone client. To facilitate future purchases on SureDone, we store your Payment Information in Stripe, which you can remove from your account at any time by sending an email to support@suredone.com. We consider your Payment Information and do not make such information public. We collect and store information created by your purchases made from a SureDone Client (" **Transaction Data** "). Transaction Data may include the SureDone client’s name and the date, time and amount of the transaction, as well as your shipping and billing information. In addition, SureDone may also collect information about your bidding, buying and selling history as well as third party comments regarding your bidding, buying and selling behavior. Bidding and buying history may specifically include your history with respect to any failure to complete sales on winning bids.  

**Third-Parties and Affiliates:** SureDone uses a variety of third-party services to help provide our Services, such as hosting our various blogs and wikis, and to help us understand and improve the use of our Services, such as Google Analytics. These third-party service providers may collect information sent by your browser as part of a web page request, such as cookies or your IP address. 

### Information Sharing and Disclosure

**Your Consent:** We may share or disclose your information at your direction, such as when you authorize a third-party web client or application to access your SureDone account.

**Service Providers:** We engage service providers to perform functions and provide services to us in the United States and abroad. We may share your private personal information with such service providers subject to confidentiality obligations consistent with this Privacy Policy, and on the condition that the third parties use your private personal data only on our behalf and pursuant to our instructions. We share your Payment Information with payment services providers to process payments; prevent, detect and investigate fraud or other prohibited activities; facilitate dispute resolution such as chargebacks or refunds; and for other purposes associated with the acceptance of credit or debit cards. We may share your credit or debit card number with payment services providers, or third parties authorized by them, to monitor card transactions at participating merchants and track redemption activity for the purposes of providing card-linked services.

**Sellers of Goods and Services:** If you buy goods from a SureDone client, we may provide the SureDone client, seller, commerce provider or marketplace with your name, email address, shipping address, Payment Information and Transaction Data to facilitate payment processing, order fulfilment and dispute resolution (including payment and shipping disputes) and to help prevent, detect and investigate fraud or other prohibited activities. Please refer to these third parties’ privacy policies for information about their privacy practices.

**Law and Harm:** Notwithstanding anything to the contrary in this Policy, we may preserve or disclose your information if we believe that it is reasonably necessary to comply with a law, regulation or legal request; to protect the safety of any person; to address fraud, security or technical issues; or to protect SureDone's rights or property. However, nothing in this Privacy Policy is intended to limit any legal defenses or objections that you may have to a third party’s, including a government’s, request to disclose your information.

**Business Transfers and Affiliates:** In the event that SureDone is involved in a bankruptcy, merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets, your information may be sold or transferred as part of that transaction. This Privacy Policy will apply to your information as transferred to the new entity.

**Non-Private or Non-Personal Information:** We may share or disclose your non-private, aggregated or otherwise non-personal information, such as your public user profile information, public product listings, or the number of users who clicked on a particular link (even if only one did).

Modifying Your Personal Information

If you are a registered user of our Services, we provide you with tools and account settings to access or modify the personal information you provided to us and associated with your account.

You can also permanently delete your SureDone account. If you email [support@suredone.com](mailto:support@suredone.com) from the email your account was created with, your account will be deactivated and then deleted. When your account is deactivated, it is not viewable on SureDone.com. For up to 30 days after deactivation it is still possible to restore your account if it was accidentally or wrongfully deactivated. After 30 days, we may begin the process of deleting your account from our systems, which can take up to a week.

Our Policy Towards Children

Our Services are not directed to persons under 13. If you become aware that your child has provided us with personal information without your consent, please contact us at privacy@SureDone.com. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we take steps to remove such information and terminate the child's account. You can find additional resources for parents and teens here.

EU Safe Harbor Framework

SureDone complies with the U.S.-E.U. and U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view our certification, please visit the U.S. Department of Commerce website.

Changes to this Policy

We may revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. The most current version of the policy will govern our use of your information and will always be at https://SureDone.com/privacy. If we make a change to this policy that, in our sole discretion, is material, we will  notify you by placing a prominant notice on the SureDone.com website for the 30 days preceeding the effective date of said change and by email to the email address associated with your account. By continuing to access or use the Services after those changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy.

_Effective: May 25, 2018_

#### View Prior Terms

Thoughts or questions about this Privacy Policy? [Please, let us know](https://www.suredone.com/contact).
